Workplace Competition Code
직장 경쟁 코드
I want to poach you
당신을 밀렵하고 싶어요
Served as the leader of the Global Communications Group
글로벌커뮤니케이션그룹 리더 역임
(Episode 3)
(에피소드 3)
please wait a moment
잠시만 기다려주세요
good
좋은
(Serong Human Resources Office)
(세롱인재지원실)
Yes, I am Park Yoon-so
네, 저는 박윤소입니다
What?
무엇?
(Admission list, Public Relations Office, Business Strategy Headquarters: Park Yoon-soo)
(입학명단, 홍보실 경영전략본부 : 박윤수)
right
오른쪽
OK, thank you
네, 감사합니다
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Miss Yun Zhao?
자오 씨?
Feel sorry
유감
What did you just say?
너 방금 뭐라고 했어?
Who called?
누가 전화했어요?
I…
나…
Admitted by Shi Rong
Shi Rong이 인정함
They have released special recruitment quotas
특별 채용 할당량을 발표했습니다.
That's it
그게 다야
(Jae Min)
(재민)
that…
저것…
Representative Xu, what you just proposed to me...
쉬 대표님, 방금 제게 제안하신 내용은...
No, nothing
더 아무것도
Next time, we'll talk about it later
다음번엔 나중에 얘기하자
Listen quickly, I should be calling to congratulate you.
빨리 들어보세요. 축하하려고 전화해야겠네요.
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
Shi Rong?
시 롱?
Yeah, I got the call. That's not a big deal.
응, 전화 받았어. 별 일 아니잖아.
Come on, of course it's amazing.
어서, 물론 놀랍습니다.
Hey, am I right?
이봐, 내 말이 맞지?
Can not believe it!
믿을 수 없어!
I just received the call
방금 전화를 받았어요
- The timing is just perfect - Oh my god
- 타이밍이 딱 맞아요 - 맙소사
Of course we should celebrate this kind of thing
물론 우리는 이런 일을 축하해야 합니다.
So I want you to promise not to push my face into the cake.
그러니까 내 얼굴을 케이크에 밀어넣지 않겠다고 약속해줬으면 좋겠어 .
Then I'll pick a really delicious cake
그럼 내가 정말 맛있는 케이크 골라줄게
Don't worry about the cake, just come.
케이크 걱정하지 말고 그냥 오세요.
There's no celebration party today
오늘은 축하파티가 없어요
Why?
왜?
She was clamoring for me to buy a cake just now
그 사람이 지금 나한테 케이크 사달라고 소리치고 있었어
I don’t know, she’s worried about how to leave her boss now.
그녀는 지금 상사를 어떻게 떠날지 걱정하고 있습니다 .
Please tell her for me that not being nervous is also a virtue.
긴장하지 않는 것도 미덕이라고 전해주세요 .
Is there such a saying?
그런 말이 있나요?
You are indeed a Chinese major, and your literary attainments are really good.
당신은 정말 한문 전공이고, 문학적 소양도 정말 좋습니다.
Hey, Xiaomin said, "Not being nervous is also a virtue."
안녕하세요 샤오민이 "긴장하지 않는 것도 미덕"이라고 하더군요.
(Jae Min)
(재민)
Hey, I'm not crazy, I'm really worried
야 나 미친 게 아니야 정말 괴로워
You have never had a good boss, so you cannot empathize with me.
당신은 좋은 상사를 만나본 적이 없기 때문에 나와 공감할 수 없습니다.
you poor guys
불쌍한 놈들
If she doesn't plan to report her death, tell her to reply quickly.
사망신고를 할 생각이 없다면 빨리 답장을 하라고 하세요.
There are still a bunch of people waiting to be replaced who don’t have to worry about their bosses.
상사에 대해 걱정할 필요가 없는 교체를 기다리는 사람들이 여전히 많이 있습니다 .
I'll close the line first
먼저 줄을 닫을게요
Did you hear that?
그거 들었어?
Is he too heartless sometimes?
그 사람은 가끔 너무 무정한가요?
But he's also the smartest among us
하지만 그 사람은 우리 중에서 가장 똑똑하기도 해
She also looks the best
역시 얘가 제일 좋아보이는데
Don't take it too seriously, I just said it casually
너무 심각하게 생각하지 마세요, 그냥 아무렇지도 않게 말한 것 뿐이에요
Forget it, you'd better sort out your thoughts.
잊어 버리세요. 생각을 정리하는 것이 좋습니다.
Hello
안녕하세요
I've already made up my mind
난 이미 결정했어
We are just friends now
우리는 이제 그냥 친구예요
Are you talking about our representatives? knew
우리 대표님 말씀이신가요? 알고 있었다
You crazy woman, really
미친 여자야, 정말
(Cao Ya Public Relations)
(카오야 홍보)
-Representative -What's wrong?
- 대표님 - 무슨 일이에요?
Are you going out?
외출 중이신가요?
Yes, I will get off work directly after finishing the meeting with the client.
네, 고객님과의 미팅을 마치고 바로 퇴근하겠습니다.
If you have nothing to do, just finish packing and go back early.
할 일 없으면 그냥 짐 싸서 일찍 돌아가세요.
-represent! -Yes, what's wrong?
-대표하다! -네, 무슨 일이에요?
-What's up? -that…
-무슨 일이야? -저것…
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
Nothing, please walk slowly
아무것도 없어요 천천히 걸어주세요
Ouch, so boring
아야, 너무 지루해
-I am leaving , bye
-나 떠난다 , 안녕
Why did she leave so early?
그녀는 왜 그렇게 일찍 떠났나요?
(Se Yong, final admission notice for the 2022 special recruitment for people with no qualifications and experience)
(세용, 2022년 무자격, 경력 무자격 특별전형 최종 합격 통보 )
(Hello, I am the person in charge of recruitment at Shirong. I would like to inform you that you have been admitted in 2022...)
(안녕하세요 시롱 채용담당자입니다. 2022년도에 합격하셨음을 알려드립니다...)
(Cao Ya Public Relations)
(카오야 홍보)
represent
대표하다
You're here, Yun Zhao
당신이 여기 있어요, 윤자오
Look at this
이거 봐요
What do you think this is?
이것이 무엇이라고 생각하시나요?
Chair?
의자?
Yeah?
응?
Then I'll make it into a chair
그럼 의자로 만들어줄게
You are a chair from now on, a chair
너는 이제부터 의자야 의자야
It's so late. Why don't you go home and come to see me instead?
너무 늦었는데 대신 집에 가서 나 보러 오는 게 어때?
I'll tell you after you finish.
끝나고 나서 말해줄게.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
What is going on? Say it
무슨 일이야? 말해
I want to have my own brand
나만의 브랜드를 갖고 싶다
In an agency, I always deal with other people’s brands.
에이전시에서는 항상 다른 사람의 브랜드를 다룹니다.
That desire began to emerge in my heart
그 소망이 내 마음 속에 나타나기 시작했어요
Of course I understand that the client's brand is actually equivalent to my...
물론 나는 클라이언트의 브랜드가 실제로 내 브랜드와 동일하다는 것을 이해합니다.
please
제발
Do you think I don't understand that feeling?
내가 그 기분을 이해하지 못할 것 같나요?
I can totally understand
나는 전적으로 이해할 수 있다
I have worked in both large companies and agencies.
저는 대기업과 대행사에서 일했습니다.
I just don’t want my dreams to come to an end in vain
내 꿈이 헛되이 끝나지 않았으면 좋겠어
I just have such a good opportunity
정말 좋은 기회가 왔네요
congratulations
축하해요
I'm proud of you, Yun Zhao
자랑스럽다 윤자오
Sorry, representative
죄송해요 대표님
What's there to be sorry for?
미안할 게 뭐 있어?
Gosh, I sure have a knack for developing talent, right?
맙소사, 나 분명 재능을 키우는 재주가 있지, 그렇지?
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Alas, just hire new people
아아, 그냥 새로운 사람을 고용하세요
Okay, it's time for us to go
알았어 이제 우리 갈 시간이야
Do you want me to have a drink with you?
나랑 한잔 할래?
Not today, next time
오늘은 말고 다음에
OK
좋아요
Are you depressed because Yun Zhao was admitted by Shi Rong ?
윤자오가 시롱에게 인정을 받아서 우울합니까 ?
How did you know?
어떻게 알았나요?
It's nothing, I just learned about it accidentally
별거 아니야 우연히 알게 됐어
Oh, this is something worth being happy about
아, 이건 기뻐할 만한 일이야
But why am I so upset?
그런데 나는 왜 이렇게 화가 났나요?
I always tell myself not to invest too much emotion , but I always forget it again and again
너무 감정에 투자하지 말라고 늘 스스로 다짐 하지만, 늘 잊어버리고 또 잊어버리곤 해요
Once I develop feelings for them, it won't end well in the end.
일단 그들에 대한 감정이 커지면 결국 좋게 끝나지 않을 것입니다.
Because they will eventually leave for a better way out
왜냐하면 그들은 결국 더 나은 길을 찾기 위해 떠날 것이기 때문이다.
I can't be their final stop
나는 그들의 마지막 정거장이 될 수 없다
Alas
아아
Hey, Dongxun, I seem drunk
야 동춘아 나 취한 것 같아
Are you so reluctant to give up?
포기하기가 너무 꺼려지나요?
right
오른쪽
Not long ago, you clearly asked me to take Park Yun Zhao away.
얼마 전 박윤자오를 데려가라고 분명히 말씀하셨는데요.
Would I feel more relieved if she went to your company ?
그녀가 당신 회사에 가면 좀 더 안심이 될까요 ?
I was also sad when you left Universal Communications, okay?
유니버설 커뮤니케이션즈를 떠날 때도 슬펐어요 .
But we meet again now
하지만 우리는 지금 다시 만나요
If we are destined, we will meet again
운명이라면 다시 만나겠지
cheers
건배
Why don't you come back to our company this time?
이번에는 우리 회사로 다시 오시지 않겠습니까?
You're such a bad boy
넌 정말 나쁜 놈이야
Hey, the position of team leader is too...
아 팀장 자리가 너무..
Let's get rid of Cao Ya's public relations.
조야의 홍보를 없애자.
The project that Cao Ya Public Relations was originally working on can be taken over by Global Communications
Cao Ya Public Relations가 원래 진행하던 프로젝트를 Global Communications가 인수할 수 있음
Both cosmetics and high-protein bread can continue to advance
화장품도 고단백 빵도 계속 발전할 수 있다
It seems you are not drunk yet
아직 취하지 않은 것 같군요
I'll make you a co-representative
공동대표로 삼아줄게
Even Shi Yong can't intervene in this kind of thing
이런 일엔 시용도 개입할 수 없어
Besides, if we join forces, we will definitely stimulate Shirong hard.
게다가 우리가 힘을 합치면 시롱이를 자극할 게 틀림없어요.
Ms. Hanako
하나코 씨
I was admitted to Shirong
시롱에 입학했어요
No, it’s not beauty, it’s world beauty
아니 미인이 아니라 세상 미인이네
It's Shirong
시롱이에요
(Today’s protagonist)
(오늘의 주인공)
-congratulations! -Congratulations, Park Yoon-soo!
-축하해요! -박윤수님, 축하드립니다!
(#job-transfersuccessful, #is actually Shirong)
(#전직성공, #실은 시롱입니다)
(#ParkAgent, #新start # enters a big company)
(#ParkAgent, #Newstart # 대기업 입사)
(#UtopiaBoss, # Drink a Cup # is Xiaoen’s treat today)
(#유토피아상사님, #한잔 #한잔하세요 #오늘은 샤오엔의 별미)
(#superexcited, #join世grong #celebration party)
(#신난다, #join세그롱 #축하파티)
(#Today’s protagonist, #是Park Agent #ice cream cake)
(#오늘의주인공 #是박요원 #아이스크림케이크)
-cheers! -bring it on!
-건배! -가져와!
congratulations!
축하해요!
-Park Yun Zhao, congratulations! -Hello!
-박윤자오, 축하해요! -안녕하세요!
Congratulations!
축하해요!
Have fun!
재미있게 보내세요!
Congratulations, Park Yoon-soo!
축하해요 박윤수님!
-Hey, cheers! -Okay, cheers!
-안녕, 건배! -좋아, 건배!
Take it!
가져!
(#开奖大公司, # Drink, #champagne)
(#开奖大公主, #음료, #샴페인)
(#ParkAgent returns, #ParkAgent has a drink)
(#파크에이전트 복귀, #파크에이전트 한잔 )
(#BrilliantSeason, #newstart)
(#BrilliantSeason, #newstart)
(# Welcome to the World #Park Yun Zhao did it, #congratulations)
(#웰컴 투 더 월드 #박윤자 님이 해냈어요 #축하해요)
-(Celebrate well!)
-(잘 축하해주세요!)
arms together
팔짱을 끼다
stretch forward
앞으로 뻗다
lower your head
머리를 숙여라
arm raised
팔을 올렸다
head up
머리를 들어라
(Se Yong)
(세용)
look to the front
앞을 봐
Turn your wrist
손목을 돌려라
then left
그 다음 떠났다
Reverse direction
역방향
stand up
일어서다
push outward
바깥쪽으로 밀어
gather towards body
몸쪽으로 모인다
arm circles
팔 서클
push outward
바깥쪽으로 밀어
stretch to the left
왼쪽으로 뻗는다
stretch to the right
오른쪽으로 뻗는다
stretch down
스트레칭하다
down
아래에
It ends here
여기서 끝
To all members of the Serong family, I wish you an energetic day.
세롱가족 여러분, 활기찬 하루 보내시기 바랍니다.
Those who do public relations these days
요즘 홍보 하시는 분들
All lack perseverance
다들 인내심이 부족해요
We used to stay up all night drinking
우리는 밤새도록 술을 마시곤 했어
I can still arrive at the company on time at 7 a.m. the next day.
나는 아직도 다음날 오전 7시에 회사에 제시간에 도착할 수 있다.
Even if you faint, you will still fall in the company
기절해도 회사에는 계속 빠진다
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
When Agent Jin comes, I will definitely tell him
진요원 오면 꼭 말해줄게
Let's go, Agent Liu
가자, 리우 요원
OK
좋아요
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Go to a team leader meeting
팀장 회의에 참석하다
He asked me to personally report to the director of the office. The media promotion strategy is not limited to the plan.
직접 실장에게 보고하라고 하더군요” 언론홍보 전략은 계획에만 국한되지 않는다.
Team leader meeting?
팀장 회의?
This sentence makes my soul feel like it has been ravaged in every possible way
이 문장은 내 영혼이 모든 면에서 황폐화된 것처럼 느끼게 만든다.
The Bible contains all the truths in the world
성경은 세상의 모든 진리를 담고 있다
It is recorded inside
안에 녹음되어 있어요
"If you seek, you will find. If you knock, the door will open to you."
"구하면 찾을 것이요, 문을 두드리면 열릴 것이니라."
There is nothing impossible in this world
이 세상에 불가능한 일은 없다
Amen
아멘
What's more, those employees who have the strength to enter our world
게다가 우리의 세계에 들어갈 수 있는 힘을 가진 직원 들은
You shouldn’t make excuses for your lack of ability…
능력이 부족하다고 변명하면 안 된다…
-Chief Chen -What's wrong?
-첸 과장 -무슨 일이야?
I'm sorry to interrupt your precious speech.
소중한 말씀을 방해해서 죄송합니다.
But there is one last item left on the agenda.
하지만 마지막 안건이 하나 남아있습니다.
It’s a public relations press release with no qualifications.
아무런 자격도 없는 홍보 보도자료입니다.
yes
예
- Yes - We haven't discussed that yet.
- 네 - 아직 논의한 바는 없습니다.
The representative asked us to exclude "Da Guo Daily"
담당자가 '대국일보'를 제외해 달라고 요청했습니다.
But the consequences of doing so may be unimaginable
하지만 그렇게 한 결과는 상상할 수 없을 수도 있습니다
However, if "Da Guo Daily" is added to the list
그러나 "대국일보"가 목록에 추가되면
-That's tantamount to disobeying the representative's order. -That's it.
-그건 대표님의 명령에 불복종하는 것과 다름없습니다 .
She has just been promoted from head office to representative
그녀는 방금 본사에서 대표로 승진했습니다.
So we should pay special attention to her feelings.
그러므로 우리는 그녀의 감정에 특별한 주의를 기울여야 합니다.
Yes, you are right
그래 네가 맞아
So I found the person in charge
그래서 담당자를 찾았어요
- You might as well listen to his opinion - Okay
- 그 사람 의견을 들어보는 게 좋을 것 같아요 - 알았어
Just send the press release to the news agency
그냥 보도자료를 통신사에 보내세요
There is no need to send it to Daguo Ilbo and the top ten central comprehensive dailies.
굳이 다국일보 나 중앙10대 종합일간지 에 보낼 필요가 없습니다 .
Anyway, whether it’s a TV station or a newspaper
어차피 방송국이든 신문이든
They all receive reports from news agencies
그들은 모두 통신사로부터 보고를 받습니다
"Daguo Daily" is not the only one who is excluded in this way.
이런 식으로 배제되는 것은 '대구오일보'만이 아니다 .
It will also be easier for us to cope with
우리도 대처하기가 더 쉬울 것입니다
sounds good
좋은 것 같아요
Just do as you say
그냥 네 말대로 해
As expected of the second group
두 번째 그룹의 예상대로
Agent Caimin, do you go to church?
카이민 요원님, 교회에 가시나요?
No, I am not religious...
아니요, 저는 종교가 없습니다...
The so-called faith…
소위 신앙..
-Chief Chen -huh?
-첸 과장님 -응?
I believe in non-discriminatory employment, regardless of qualifications
나는 자격에 관계없이 차별 없는 고용을 믿습니다.
is a good starting point
좋은 출발점이다
But why is it our group?
그런데 왜 우리 그룹일까요?
Dear Shirong employees
친애하는 시롱 임직원 여러분
nice to meet you
만나서 반가워요
Given that economies of scale are rapidly…
규모의 경제가 빠르게 진행되고 있다는 점을 고려하면…
If you are recruiting employees from the public relations department this time,
이번에 홍보부서 직원을 모집하신다면,
Then they should be assigned to the group that plans and executes the project.
그런 다음 프로젝트를 계획하고 실행하는 그룹 에 배정되어야 합니다 .
Suddenly putting people into our group will really make it difficult for us to do things.
갑자기 사람들을 우리 그룹에 포함시키면 우리가 일을 하기가 정말 어려워질 것입니다.
Director Chen
첸 감독
- I thought the matter was settled - Yes, it was settled
- 문제가 해결된 줄 알았는데 - 네, 해결됐어요
But I never agreed
하지만 난 동의한 적이 없어
You didn't come to the meeting yourself
당신은 회의에 직접 오지 않았습니다
I asked to change the meeting time , but you still held the meeting as usual
회의 시간을 변경해 달라고 했는데 여전히 평소대로 회의를 진행하고 계셨습니다.
If you are unable to attend the meeting due to personal matters , you will have to bear the consequences yourself.
개인사정으로 인해 회의에 참석하지 못하실 경우 그에 따른 책임은 본인이 져야 합니다.
This is a company
이것은 회사입니다
Can't you be a little more flexible in what you do?
당신이 하는 일에 좀 더 유연해질 수는 없나요?
This matter is not that urgent
이 문제는 그다지 긴급하지 않습니다
Pool leader
풀 리더
if that is the case
그렇다면
Still have to open it again...
그래도 다시 열어야지...
No, no need
아니요, 필요하지 않습니다.
Team Leader Chi is just making trouble unreasonably.
치 팀장은 무리하게 말썽만 피우고 있어요.
This matter is a foregone conclusion
이 문제는 기정사실이다
Besides, that employee also came to report today.
게다가 오늘 그 직원도 보고하러 왔어요.
Pool leader
풀 리더
You take people away first
당신이 먼저 사람을 데려가세요
Anyway...
그래도...
-Okay, then I'll start... -That's it.
-좋아, 그럼 시작해볼까... -그게 다야.
So that concludes today’s team leader meeting
이상으로 오늘 팀장 회의를 마치겠습니다.
-ok -very good
-그래 아주 좋다
Yes, good work
응, 잘했어
Hello, Chi Yinzhen
안녕하세요, Chi Yinzhen 님
Haven't you seen her resume?
그 사람 이력서 못 봤어?
She works in digital PR
그녀는 디지털 PR 분야에서 일하고 있습니다
These days, anyone can say that they are in digital public relations.
요즘은 누구나 디지털홍보를 하고 있다고 할 수 있습니다.
I can't believe that.
나는 그것을 믿을 수 없다.
So what do you want?
그래서 당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
Let her join your group!
그녀를 당신의 그룹에 합류시키세요!
Honestly, I recommend the person who doesn't meet the qualifications.
솔직히 자격조건 안맞는 분 추천드립니다.
It's obviously you, because that's how it's topical
분명히 너야, 그게 화제가 되니까
Hello!
안녕하세요!
Be careful what you say, you know?
말 조심하세요, 아시죠?
All the newcomers from the past also joined our group.
과거에 새로 온 사람들도 모두 우리 그룹에 합류했습니다.
Do you want our three groups to sit back and wait for death?
우리 세 그룹이 앉아서 죽음을 기다리기를 원하십니까?
That's the good thing about being in the public relations room. You can take a break and have a cup of coffee.
홍보실에 있어서 좋은 점은 커피 한잔 마시며 잠시 쉬어갈 수 있다는 점입니다.
Has Hou Ji come to work?
허지님 회사에 오셨나요?
Damn Kim Ho-gil
젠장 김호길
Speaking of that brat
그 새끼 얘기하면
you know him now
너 이제 그 사람 알지?
Didn't he even reveal which reporters he was drinking with?
어느 기자랑 술을 마셨는지도 밝히지 않았나요?
Well managed
잘 관리됨
He will stand out
그는 눈에 띌 것이다
In my opinion, he will only last three years
내 생각엔 그 사람은 3년밖에 못 버틸 것 같아
He will definitely leave his job within three years and start his own company.
그는 반드시 3년 안에 직장을 그만두고 자신의 회사를 시작할 것입니다.
Look, this is a common tactic used by people who love to flatter reporters.
보세요, 이것은 기자들에게 아첨하는 것을 좋아하는 사람들이 사용하는 일반적인 전술 입니다.
This, I'm not interested
이거, 난 관심 없어
me too
저도요
By the way, Team Leader Chi just said something strange.
그런데 치 팀장이 방금 이상한 말을 했어요.
What words?
어떤 단어?
She said that Team Leader Song strongly recommended Park Yun-soo for this recruitment.
이번 채용에는 송팀장이 박윤수 선수를 적극 추천했다는 것이다.
Yeah?
응?
Really?
정말?
Do you really have no idea?
정말 모르시나요?
Yeah, I really don't know
응, 난 정말 모르겠어
But how could he push her?
하지만 그가 어떻게 그녀를 밀어낼 수 있었을까?
Didn't you do a blind test at the beginning?
처음에는 블라인드 테스트를 하지 않았나요?
anyway
그래도
Do you know that person who admitted with any qualifications?
어떤 자격으로 합격한 사람을 아시나요?
Otherwise, why would you be interested?
그렇지 않다면 왜 관심을 가지겠습니까?
Because that's what I'm responsible for
그건 내가 책임지는 거니까
That being said, you're acting a little suspicious.
즉, 당신은 약간 의심스러운 행동을 하고 있습니다.
It's time for us to go back
이제 우리는 돌아갈 시간이야
You know me, right?
저 아시죠?
I have God-given intuition.
나는 하나님이 주신 직관을 가지고 있습니다.
I feel it now
이제 느껴져
Stop drinking coffee and have a beer.
커피 그만 마시고 맥주 한잔 하세요.
Or do you want soju?
아니면 소주 드릴까요?
All right
괜찮은
Hello
안녕하세요
This is the big conference hall
여기가 큰 회의장이에요
And here is…
그리고 여기는…
Agent Jin, this is a newcomer
진요원 신인이에요
-Hello _
- 안녕하세요 _
-Okay -I'll go first then
- 알았어 - 그럼 나 먼저 갈게
Please over there
저기로 부탁해요
This is the newcomer who will join us in the future, Ms. Zheng Zhiren.
앞으로 우리와 함께 할 신인 Zheng Zhiren 씨입니다.
Say hello
인사해
Please give me some advice
조언 좀 부탁드려요
This is your main work area in the future
이것은 미래의 주요 작업 영역입니다.
(Public Relations Group, Team Leader, Cui Yonghao)
(홍보그룹 최용하오 팀장)
Public Relations Group 2
홍보그룹 2
Team leader Song Xuantai
팀장 송쉬안타이
-He... -Super annoying.
-그는... - 정말 짜증나.
No, it's super strong
아니요, 엄청 강해요
(Team leader, Song Xuantai)
(팀장 송쉬안타이)
He's really super strong
그 사람 정말 엄청 강해요
Also, let’s just pretend we don’t know each other in the company.
그리고 회사에서는 그냥 모르는 척 하자.
Because I hope to rely on myself for everything
모든 걸 나 자신에게만 의지하고 싶으니까
Can you understand?
너 이해할 수 있니?
up to you
당신한테 달렸습니다
Really
정말
Then why are you receiving special training now?
그렇다면 지금은 왜 특별훈련을 받고 있는가?
(Public Relations Group Three, Team Leader, Chi Yinzhen)
(홍보그룹 3 팀장 Chi Yinzhen)
Public Relations Group 3, also the Digital Public Relations Group
홍보 그룹 3(디지털 홍보 그룹이기도 함)
The team leader is Chi Yinzhen
팀 리더는 Chi Yinzhen입니다.
She was the first to become a team leader among those who were publicly recruited at the same time.
동시에 공개채용된 사람들 중 가장 먼저 팀장이 된 인물 이다.
He is also the only deputy chief appointed as the team leader.
그는 팀장으로 임명된 유일한 부단장이기도 하다.
Team leader Chi, this is Miss Park Yun-jo
치 팀장 박윤조 선생님 입니다
nice to meet you
만나서 반가워요
My name is Chi Yinzhen
내 이름은 치인젠이에요
Then I'll excuse you first.
그럼 먼저 실례하겠습니다.
Our group…
우리 그룹은…
Agent Xu
쉬 요원
Yes, Team Leader Chi
응, 치 팀장
Let’s get to know each other
서로 알아가자
My name is Park Yun-soo, I'm new here
제 이름은 박윤수입니다. 처음 들어왔습니다.
Hello, I'm Xu He, nice to meet you
안녕하세요, 저는 Xu He입니다. 만나서 반갑습니다.
He is a designer personally hired by the digital public relations team to strengthen the design field.
디자인 분야 강화를 위해 디지털홍보팀 에서 직접 고용한 디자이너 다.
He is in a state of being drained of energy
에너지가 고갈된 상태다.
Pool leader
풀 리더
Have you read the draft I sent you earlier?
아까 보내드린 초안 읽어보셨나요?
I'll watch that after the meeting.
회의 후에 시청하겠습니다.
OK
좋아요
Agent Xu, you also need to have a meeting together.
Xu 요원님, 당신도 함께 회의를 해야 합니다.
But I still have a lot to do…
하지만 아직 할 일이 많아요…
Agent Park, this is your seat
박요원 여기가 네 자리야
Let's go
갑시다
"Agent Park"?
"박요원"?
I haven’t heard anyone call me Agent Park for a long time.
오랫동안 나를 박요원이라고 부르는 사람이 없었습니다.
By the way, the public relations office uses open recruitment
그런데 홍보실에서는 공개채용을 하고 있어요
The only new person admitted is in the third group
새로 입학한 유일한 사람은 세 번째 그룹에 있습니다.
Otherwise, why would I come to work in a place like this?
그렇지 않으면 내가 왜 이런 곳에 일하러 오겠는가?
No work-life balance , even the salary sucks
일과 삶의 균형도 없고 월급도 형편 없다
Then just leave
그럼 그냥 떠나
Yes, that's what I meant, so I'm going to stop doing it from today on
응, 그런 뜻이었으니까 오늘부터 그만 할게요.
Could it be that you are the one who has no qualifications...
혹시 자격도 없는 분이신 건 아닐까...
Unexpectedly, we met again
뜻밖에도 우리는 다시 만났어요
It seems we are really destined
우리는 정말 운명인 것 같아
what is this? Am I dreaming?
이게 뭔가요? 저 꿈꾸고 있나요?
I can hear everything
난 다 들을 수 있어
(Se Yong)
(세용)
(Announcement: Personnel Appointment Notice)
(공지사항 : 인사발령 공고)
Do you know about this?
당신은 이것에 대해 알고 있습니까?
Yes, Director Chen
네, 첸 감독님
Yes, okay, I'll go there now
응, 알았어, 지금 거기로 갈게
Team Leader Cui!
팀장 추이!
(Personnel Appointment Announcement Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
(인사공고 구이정 홍보실장)
She was hired to be the chief public relations officer and executive director?
그녀는 최고홍보책임자 겸 전무이사로 채용되었나요?
Se Yong's chief public relations officer?
세용홍보실장?
It's really unheard of
정말 들어본 적도 없는 일이야
Then isn't she our direct supervisor?
그렇다면 그 사람은 우리의 직속 상사가 아닌가?
That's why everyone is in a mess now
그래서 지금은 다들 혼란스러워
The chief public relations officer is the immediate boss of the public relations office
최고홍보책임자는 홍보실의 직속 상사이다.
But the PR office knew nothing about this personnel appointment?
그런데 홍보실에서는 이번 인사에 대해 아무것도 몰랐다고?
Will Director Chen be fired?
첸 감독은 해고될까?
It's hard to say. The life span of a high-level boss can be described as life and death.
말하기는 어렵지만, 고위보스의 수명은 삶과 죽음으로 요약될 수 있다.
Why didn't you say a word?
왜 한마디도 안 했어?
(Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
(구이정 홍보실장)
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
Is it someone you know?
아는 사람인가요?
Don't you know this person?
이 사람을 모르시나요?
Yes, Agent Jae Min
네, 재민요원님
I don't know who she is
나는 그녀가 누구인지 모른다
“Gizada”
“기자다”
This name is so funny
이름이 너무 웃겨요
So who is she?
그렇다면 그녀는 누구입니까?
It's really her
정말 그 사람이에요
Cable News Network has also published several interviews with her.
Cable News Network는 또한 그녀와의 여러 인터뷰를 발표했습니다 .
She is a public relations expert
그녀는 홍보 전문가이다
Is she coming to our company?
그 사람 우리 회사에 오나요?
hello
안녕하세요
Thanks
감사해요
Director Gu
구 이사
Um
음
The company should make an announcement now
회사는 지금 발표해야 한다
But it's time to get off work now
하지만 이제 퇴근 시간이야
This is the representative's instruction
대표님의 지시사항입니다
You will be staying in the same hotel as the representative for the time being
당분간 대표님과 같은 호텔에 투숙하게 됩니다.
You do not mind right?
괜찮지 않나요?
I'm very mind
나는 매우 마음이
But what else can be done?
하지만 또 무엇을 할 수 있습니까?
I can only find a place to live as soon as possible
하루빨리 살 곳만 찾을 수 있어
Right?
오른쪽?
Director of Strategy Office, Director of Human Resources Office , Director of Secretarial Office
전략실장, 인사실장 , 비서실장
Only these few people know about this
이 사실을 아는 사람은 극소수
Of course, this is what Representative Lin meant
물론 린 대표가 한 말은 이것이다.
No one knows what she is thinking
그녀가 무슨 생각을 하는지 아무도 모르지
They actually created a new position of chief public relations officer and brought people back.
그들은 실제로 최고홍보책임자(CPR)라는 새로운 직책을 만들어 사람들을 다시 불러들였습니다.
She must have drunk too much foreign ink , so she doesn’t understand how things work in Korea.
그녀는 외국 잉크를 너무 많이 마셔서 한국 상황이 어떻게 돌아가는지 이해하지 못하는 것 같습니다.
I'm worried she'll do other ridiculous things
그 사람이 또 다른 말도 안되는 짓을 할까봐 걱정돼요
This was the first thing she prepared after taking office as the representative director.
대표이사 취임 후 가장 먼저 준비한 일 이었다.
I think she should have her own plan
내 생각엔 그 사람도 자기만의 계획이 있어야 할 것 같아
Go and inquire more carefully
가서 좀 더 자세히 물어보세요
Let’s see what kind of work she does mainly
주로 어떤 일을 하는지 살펴볼까요?
Yes, I understand
네 이해했습니다
Since she became a representative
대표가 된 이후로
The position of the head of the Strategy Headquarters is now vacant.
현재 전략본부장 자리는 공석이다.
If there is a suitable candidate, please introduce it to me.
적합한 후보자가 있다면 소개해주세요.
People from our camp?
우리 캠프 사람들이요?
suitable person
적합한 사람
Yes, I understand
네 이해했습니다
(Vice President, Zheng Qiurong)
(부회장 정추룽)
It's time to get off work
퇴근할 시간이다
Let me see…
좀 보자…
OK, let's go
확인 가자
what time is it now?
지금 몇 시야?
It turns out it’s already so late
이미 너무 늦었다는 걸 알게 됐어
Hey, did you hear that? There's a new chief public relations officer in the public relations office.
야, 그거 들었어? 홍보실에 새로운 최고홍보책임자가 왔습니다.
Chief public relations officer?
최고 홍보 책임자?
-What's that for? -I don't know either
- 그게 뭔데요? -나도 모르겠어요
It seems there was an announcement just now
방금 공지가 나왔던 것 같네요
Yeah?
응?
You drink coffee, right?
너 커피 마시는구나, 그렇지?
Thank you
감사합니다
You seem to get off work very late
당신은 아주 늦게 퇴근하는 것 같아요
How can I help?
내가 어떻게 도움이 될 수 있습니다?
(Se Yong, login)
(세용, 로그인)
I heard that after the personnel appointment announcement was released, there was a lot of discussion throughout the company.
인사 공고가 나온 뒤 회사 전체에서 많은 논의가 있었다고 들었습니다.
But I don't have permission to log into the company intranet yet
그런데 아직 회사 인트라넷에 로그인할 수 있는 권한이 없습니다.
(Welcome to the World Internet)
(세계 인터넷에 오신 것을 환영합니다)
(Personnel Appointment Announcement Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
(인사공고 구이정 홍보실장)
"Gizada"?
"기자다"?
I'm going to work
나는 일하러 갈거야
- Goo Yi Jung - What?
- 구이정 - 뭐?
She is that Goo Yi Jung, right?
그 사람 구이정 맞죠?
-Don’t you know Goo Yi Jung? -I really don't know who she is
- 구이정을 모르시나요? -나는 그 사람이 누구인지 정말 모른다.
Not really possible today
오늘은 정말 불가능해
- Just promise me this time! What's wrong? -ah
- 이번엔 꼭 약속해! 뭐가 문제 야? -아
Brother Zhejun, wait, this is very important.
Zhejun 형제 님, 잠깐만 요. 이건 매우 중요합니다.
Is the new chief public relations officer the same Goo Yi-jung?
신임 홍보실장은 구이정씨와 같은 사람 인가 ?
Yes, she is the public relations expert who appeared in that internationally renowned magazine this time.
네, 그녀는 이번에 국제적으로 유명한 잡지에 등장한 홍보 전문가 입니다.
That's Goo Yi Jung
구이정이네
-Yoo Jae-min! -Oh my god
-유재민! -맙소사
- Wait, wait a minute - Please, just once
- 잠깐만, 잠깐만 - 제발 한 번만요
I beg you, I beg you
부탁해요, 부탁해요
-Jaemin! -no!
-재민! -아니요!
(Serong hopes to strengthen its public relations capabilities by introducing new senior executives)
(세롱은 새로운 고위 임원진을 영입해 홍보 역량을 강화할 예정이다)
Hey, please confirm
아 확인해주세요
OK, thanks
알았어 고마워
A publication published by a little-known company like this
이렇게 잘 알려지지 않은 회사 에서 출판한 출판물
Besides company employees, who else would read it?
회사 직원 외에 또 누가 읽을까요?
boss
사장
Do you know this person?
이 사람을 아시나요?
who is she?
그녀는 누구입니까?
She left Zter not long ago
그녀는 얼마 전 Zter를 떠났어요
Switched to public relations career for American start-up companies
미국 스타트업 기업 홍보 경력으로 전환
what are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
I'm not going to spend my whole life making company publications.
나는 회사 출판물을 만드는 데 평생을 허비하지 않을 것입니다.
I want to be like her in the future
나는 미래에 그녀처럼되고 싶다
She should have also produced company publications in the beginning.
그녀는 처음에 회사 출판물도 제작했어야 했습니다.
Have you confirmed it?
확인하셨나요?
Yes, let me confirm
네, 확인하겠습니다
Really
정말
Alas
아아
(Coco Promotional Event, we are having a meeting)
(코코 프로모션 이벤트, 미팅중입니다)
(Xiao Zhao, exhausted, dreamed that Duke Zhou was gone)
(소소는 지쳐서 주공이 사라지는 꿈을 꾸었다)
(Li Sejiang, happy birthday)
(리세장, 생일 축하해요)
(Tonight you and I will become one)
(오늘 밤 너와 나는 하나가 될 거야)
-(Keep on partying...)
-(계속 파티하세요...)
- (Drink a drink...)
- (한잔 마셔...)
(We're going to drink until we can't drink anymore. Let's have another drink)
(더 이상 못 마실 때까지 마실 거예요. 한 잔 더 마시자)
OK, come together
응, 같이 가자
- (Drink a drink)
- (음료를 마시다)
The wine is going down my throat
와인이 목으로 넘어가네
-Keep drinking!
-계속 마셔!
very good!
매우 좋은!
-good
-좋은
Everyone, sit down, sit down...
다들 앉으세요, 앉으세요...
Hello! Don't sit down. What are you doing sitting down? What's wrong?
안녕하세요! 앉지 말고 앉아서 뭐해요? 뭐가 문제 야?
Oh my god, my daughter is back.
맙소사, 내 딸이 돌아왔다.
-my daughter -she's so beautiful
- 내 딸 - 정말 예뻐요
Welcome back!
돌아온 것을 환영합니다!
-Saeyong!
-세용!
-What's wrong?
-뭐가 문제 야?
-pocket money!
-용돈!
Continue to the third stall!
계속해서 세 번째 부스로 가세요!
-good! Go to the third stall! -good!
-좋은! 세 번째 부스로 이동! -좋은!
Come on, keep on partying!
자, 계속 파티를 즐겨보세요!
Awesome…
엄청난…
marvelous
기이
Come, have another drink
와서 한 잔 더 마셔
It tastes so good, it just gets better.
맛이 너무 좋아서 더 좋아지네요.
Where are you?
어디세요?
(Kaiming)
(카이밍)
I'm going to spend the night at a friend's house
친구 집에서 하룻밤을 보낼 예정이에요
- (Let's have a drink)
- (한 잔 하자)
Have you been back?
돌아오셨나요?
So annoying
너무 짜증나
The guard guy kept running up , and even the police came
경비아저씨가 계속 달려오는데 경찰까지 와요
By the way, when you pay me, you will help me buy a pair of brand-name sneakers.
그건 그렇고, 당신이 나에게 돈을 지불하면 내가 유명 브랜드 운동화 한 켤레를 사는 데 도움을 줄 것입니다.
Get away
떠나라
(Se Yong)
(세용)
Ouch, I'm almost exhausted
아야, 거의 지쳤어
Hello
안녕하세요
-Hi -Hmm
-안녕하세요 -흠
Why don't you give me some hints?
나한테 힌트 좀 주지 그래?
unacceptable
받아들일 수 없는
That's a special instruction from the representative. I have to keep it a secret.
대표님이 특별히 지시하신 사항이라 비밀로 해야겠습니다.
but
하지만
I really can't understand
정말 이해할 수가 없어요
Just add a rank above the director of the public relations office
홍보실장보다 한 직급만 더하면 된다
Is it necessary to make it look like an espionage war?
굳이 간첩전쟁처럼 보이게 할 필요가 있을까?
-I don’t know about that either. -Young Master
- 그건 나도 잘 모르겠어 - 영 스승님
I am not kidding
농담 아니야
Maybe the head of the strategy room will know
아마 전략실장이라면 알겠지
He doesn't answer the phone at all
그 사람은 전화를 전혀 받지 않아요
Chief Kim called me just now
김과장님이 방금 전화했어요
He said that the vice president asked him to find someone who could be the head of the Strategy Headquarters.
부사장이 전략본부장을 맡을 만한 사람을 찾아보라고 했다고 한다.
What?
무엇?
In other words, if even the head of the Strategy Headquarters is from the vice president's side...
즉, 전략본부장마저도 부사장 측 출신이라면...
That means...
그 의미는...
She will become in name only
그녀는 이름뿐이 될 것이다
You should know how much the vice president loves the media, right?
부통령이 언론을 얼마나 사랑하는지 아셔야겠죠?
He still reads the newspaper every day
그는 아직도 매일 신문을 읽는다
You need to prepare a plan for this time that the qualifications are not restricted.
자격이 제한되지 않는 이때를 위한 계획을 준비해야 합니다.
Try to be as high-profile as possible
가능한 한 유명해 지도록 노력하십시오
Cai Min
카이 민
yes
예
this
이것
(Publicity strategy for the plan of independent qualifications, Public Relations Office, Park Yoon-so)
(자격자격 기획홍보전략, 홍보실 박윤소)
Help me think of some more powerful moves to strengthen them.
그들을 강화할 수 있는 좀 더 강력한 움직임을 생각하도록 도와주세요.
(Internal company channel interview)
(사내 채널 인터뷰)
(Newspaper interview, magazine interview, TV interview)
(신문 인터뷰, 잡지 인터뷰, TV 인터뷰)
(Publicity strategy for the plan of independent qualifications, Public Relations Office, Park Yoon-so)
(자격자격 기획홍보전략, 홍보실 박윤소)
That, Team Leader Chi
저, 치 팀장
-What's up? -What should I do next?
-무슨 일이야? -다음에는 어떻게 해야 하나요?
Go investigate the Serong Public Relations Office
세롱 홍보실에 조사하러 가세요
-Business results to date -Yes
-현재까지의 사업실적 -예
Then I'll confirm the information first and then contact you.
그러면 먼저 내용을 확인한 후 연락드리겠습니다.
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
(Hummer achieved sales of KRW 1 trillion with self-developed products )
(허머 자체 개발 제품으로 매출 1조원 달성)
(March 2022, news clipping)
(2022년 3월 뉴스클리핑)
Hey, look outside
야, 밖 좀 봐
- it's a garden - and there's a garden
- 정원이에요 - 그리고 정원도 있어요
Yes, we have a garden
네, 정원이 있어요
-Hello -you are here
-안녕하세요 - 당신은 여기 있습니다
right
오른쪽
No one will use that bar
아무도 그 바를 사용하지 않을 것이다
That's Representative Xu's office
그곳이 쉬대표 사무실이에요
There is the conference room
회의실이 있어요
That's my office
거기가 내 사무실이야
Why would you buy something like this?
왜 이런 걸 사겠습니까?
Representative, Global Communication is beautiful
대표님, 글로벌 커뮤니케이션이 아름답다
Beautiful, right?
아름답죠?
Because Dongxun majored in design
동훈이 디자인을 전공했으니까
He decorated this place himself
이 곳을 직접 꾸몄어요
He's really talented
그는 정말 재능이 있어요
He will come over later, let's have dinner together
그 사람 나중에 올 거야, 같이 저녁 먹자
Of course I am honored to have dinner with these two representatives.
물론 이 두 대표님과 함께 저녁식사를 할 수 있어서 영광입니다.
How are you doing in this world?
이 세상에서 어떻게 지내세요?
It's great. Everyone is very kind to me.
훌륭해요. 다들 나에게 매우 친절해요.
I have something I want to tell you face to face
얼굴을 마주하고 말하고 싶은 게 있어요
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
Hello
안녕하세요
Yun Zhao, Shi Rong wants to get your plan
Yun Zhao, Shi Rong은 당신의 계획을 얻고 싶어합니다
I only found out later
나중에서야 알았어
Shirong
시롱
Intend to adopt your plan
당신의 계획을 채택할 의향이 있습니다
(Sildis’ online and offline event proposals, Cao Ya Public Relations)
(실디스의 온·오프라인 이벤트 제안, Cao Ya Public Relations)
I've always wanted to tell you
난 항상 당신에게 말하고 싶었어요
But I can't find the right time
하지만 적절한 시간을 찾을 수 없어
represent
대표하다
I wrote this proposal as Cao Ya's public relations staff .
저는 조야 홍보담당자 로서 이 제안서를 작성했습니다 .
Since you're working here now, it's up to you to take over.
당신이 지금 여기서 일하고 있으니, 그 일을 맡는 것은 당신에게 달려 있습니다.
Shi Rong still doesn’t know that I’m working here.
Shi Rong은 내가 여기서 일하고 있다는 것을 아직도 모릅니다.
They want to spread the word around the world and it’s up to them.
그들은 전 세계에 소식을 전파하고 싶어하며 그것은 그들에게 달려 있습니다.
I see
알겠어요
I…
나…
Can you leave first?
먼저 떠날 수 있나요?
Let’s have dinner next time, Representative
대표님, 다음에 저녁 먹자
no problem
괜찮아요
Senior, why did Miss Yun Zhao just leave?
선배, 자오 선생님은 왜 그냥 가셨나요?
I told her about the plan
나는 그녀에게 계획에 대해 말했다.
I think it's up to me to say
내 생각엔 내가 말할 몫인 것 같아
sorry
죄송합니다
what are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
That was an offer that was impossible to refuse.
거절할 수 없는 제안이었다.
No, it should be said to be an order
아니 명령이라고 해야 하나
So don't take it too seriously
그러니 너무 심각하게 받아들이지 마세요.
But I still feel very guilty for her
하지만 나는 아직도 그 사람에 대해 큰 죄책감을 느낍니다.
That's true
그건 사실이야
I really feel sorry for her, that's right
그 사람한테 정말 미안해요, 그렇죠
(Eligibility is not subject to program promotion strategy)
(자격은 프로그램 홍보 전략에 영향을 받지 않습니다)
(Public Relations Office, Park Yun-soo)
(홍보실 박윤수)
no
아니요
To drain her of all her worth
그녀의 모든 가치를 빼앗기 위해
Just having to digest these schedules is enough to leave her with no time to do other work.
이 스케줄을 소화하는 것만으로도 그녀는 다른 일을 할 시간이 없다.
What other job does she have?
그녀는 또 어떤 직업을 갖고 있나요?
Hey, this is her job
야, 이게 그 사람 일이야
Become an Advocate for the Eligibility-Free Program
무자격 프로그램 옹호자가 되어 보세요
That's why she was admitted
그렇기 때문에 그녀는 입학을 하게 되었습니다.
But it’s time to stop.
하지만 이제는 그만둘 시간이다.
I will reschedule
일정을 다시 잡겠습니다
Agent Liu
리우 요원
Hello! Agent Liu!
안녕하세요! 리우 요원!
Yes, team leader
응, 팀장
How is the global communications plan going?
글로벌 커뮤니케이션 계획은 어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
-Sildis' project -The other party has not yet given a definite reply.
-실디스의 프로젝트 -상대방은 아직 명확한 답변을 내놓지 않았습니다.
what are they going to do
그들이 뭘하려는 건가요
Why? Have you made it clear to them?
왜? 그들에게 분명히 밝혔나요?
Can't you even convey the company's intentions well?
회사의 의도도 잘 전달되지 않나요?
It seems like you're just relaying it like a megaphone again
또 확성기처럼 전달하는 것 같은데
Didn't understand the meaning at all
의미를 전혀 이해하지 못했어요
Do you really have a way to manage those agencies well?
정말 그 기획사들을 잘 관리할 수 있는 방법이 있나요 ?
Go back and explain it clearly to them.
돌아가서 그들에게 명확하게 설명하십시오.
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
내가 말하려는 것을 이해합니까?
Please use your brain, Jaemin.
두뇌를 사용하세요, 재민님.
so what you mean is
그래서 당신이 말하는 것은
We adopt the plan from Cao Ya Public Relations
Cao Ya Public Relations의 계획을 채택합니다.
Completely out of necessity
완전히 부득이하게
Because all team leaders were not hired through open recruitment.
팀장을 모두 공개채용으로 채용하지 않았기 때문이다 .
I have the support of Minister Kim behind me.
내 뒤에는 김 장관의 지지가 있다.
Therefore, Global Media should arbitrarily steal other people’s plans.
그러므로 글로벌미디어는 남의 기획을 임의로 도용해야 한다.
Or you have to spend your own money to buy it.
아니면 자기 돈을 들여서 사야 합니다.
Is this what you want to convey?
이것이 당신이 전하고 싶은 것인가요?
Yes, that's right
네, 맞습니다
-That's what it means . -Okay, then I get it.
-그게 바로 그 뜻이에요 -그럼 알겠습니다.
That madman
그 미친놈
I seem to see myself when I was young
어린 시절의 내 모습을 보는 것 같다
Go crazy and deny your relatives
미친 듯이 친척을 부정하고
Team Leader Cui!
팀장 추이!
I shouted too loudly
너무 크게 소리쳤어요
this
이것
smokes
담배를 피우다
I don't want to smoke
나는 담배를 피우고 싶지 않아요
Just now, Team Leader Song
지금은 송팀장
Did you run away in despair?
절망에 빠져 도망쳤나요?
He must feel so embarrassed
그 사람이 너무 당황스러워할 것 같아
He certainly never thought that those words he said would turn Yijun against him.
그는 자신이 한 말이 이준을 자신에게 적대시하게 만들 것이라고는 결코 생각하지 못했습니다.
Alas, Agent Liu
아아, 리우 요원
I appreciate your madness very much
나는 당신의 광기에 매우 감사합니다
If it were me, I would be fired immediately
나였으면 바로 해고당했을텐데
It seems that the trump card is still the trump card even if it goes astray.
비장의 카드는 길을 잃더라도 여전히 비장의 카드인 것 같습니다.
This society is really unfair, right?
이 사회는 정말 불공평하지 않나요?
i was chosen
나는 선택되었다
What do you want from me?
나한테서 뭘 원하는 거야?
Mad Ace
매드 에이스
It's up to you to decide
결정하는 것은 당신에게 달려 있습니다
-why me? -This is your job.
-왜 나야? -이것이 당신의 일입니다.
- But not anymore - Are you kidding me?
- 하지만 더 이상은 아니야 - 농담하는 거야?
Didn’t you say you must be promoted this time?
이번에는 승진해야 한다고 하지 않았나요?
Without this, you're totally screwed
이거 없으면 완전 망해요
correct
옳은
i am being punished
나는 벌을 받고 있어요
As long as you know
당신이 아는 한
Let’s talk about this plan
이 계획에 대해 이야기해보자
Was it the Cao Ya public relations employee with no qualifications who did it?
그런 일을 한 사람이 자격도 없는 차오야 홍보직원이었나 ?
The representative of Cao Ya PR worked in Serong before.
Cao Ya PR 대표는 이전에 Serong에서 근무했습니다.
When we were pitching proposals, I told her that the finalist was already determined to be Global Communications
우리가 제안서를 제출할 때 이미 최종 후보가 글로벌 커뮤니케이션즈로 결정되었다고 말했습니다.
Ask her not to have high expectations
그녀에게 큰 기대를 갖지 말라고 부탁하세요
But it turned out like this
그런데 이렇게 됐다.
-Why is it always so bad? -because we made a mess
-왜 항상 그렇게 나쁜가요? -우리가 엉망으로 만들었으니까
Do you know the posts about Shi Yong in the Nonsense Forum ?
넌센스 포럼에 시용 에 관한 글을 아시나요?
Why is it always less than other companies?
왜 항상 다른 회사보다 적나요?
-Because everyone gave up? -no
-모두가 포기했기 때문에? -아니요
It’s because what we do lets others know
우리가 하는 일이 다른 사람들에게 알려지기 때문이에요
I really couldn’t hold my head up, so everyone couldn’t hold back from writing.
제가 정말 고개를 들 수가 없어서 다들 글을 쓰는 걸 참을 수가 없었어요.
I totally understand
나는 완전히 이해한다
Don't call her "regardless of qualifications" anymore
더 이상 '자격 상관없이'라고 부르지 마세요.
I want to call her Agent Park Yoon-so
박윤소 요원이라고 부르고 싶다
What?
무엇?
Yes, that’s right, I like her. I’ve had a crush on her for a long time. Are you satisfied?
네, 맞아요, 좋아해요. 오랫동안 짝사랑했어요. 만족하시나요?
What?
무엇?
So is the global communications team responsible for Sirdis' project ?
그렇다면 Sirdis의 프로젝트를 담당하는 글로벌 커뮤니케이션 팀이 있습니까 ?
Yes
예
I heard that it is currently supervised by Representative Seo Donghun personally.
현재는 서동훈 대표가 직접 총괄하고 있다고 들었습니다.
Really?
정말?
Who will be responsible for those three groups?
그 세 그룹을 누가 책임질 것인가?
I'm willing to give it a try
나는 그것을 시도해 볼 의향이 있습니다
you are not qualified yet
당신은 아직 자격이 없습니다
It seems that I can only take responsibility personally.
개인적으로 책임을 질 수 밖에 없는 것 같습니다.
That’s why I ask that qualifications be taken into consideration when replacing people.
그래서 사람을 교체할 때 자격을 고려해 달라고 요청하는 것입니다.
Pool leader
풀 리더
Change to next project
다음 프로젝트로 변경
This plan…
이 계획은…
I said I'm responsible
내가 책임이 있다고 말했어
Any questions?
질문이 있으신가요?
No
아니요
nothing
아무것도 아님
(Se Yong)
(세용)
Pool leader
풀 리더
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
About the Sildis Plan that Global Communications is responsible for
글로벌커뮤니케이션즈가 담당하는 실디스플랜(Sildis Plan) 에 대하여
That's actually the plan I made
사실 내가 세운 계획이 그거였어
Then what?
그리고 뭐?
Please leave the Sildis plan to me.
실디스의 계획은 나에게 맡겨주세요.
Please let me work on this project with Global Communications
글로벌커뮤니케이션즈에서 이 프로젝트를 진행하게 해주세요.
I am confident that I will do better than anyone else
나는 누구보다 잘할 자신이 있다
no
아니요
Please familiarize yourself with your current job content first
현재 직무 내용을 먼저 숙지하시기 바랍니다.
-Team Leader Chi -You can get off work now
- 치 팀장 - 이제 퇴근해도 돼요
Pool leader
풀 리더
It only takes a few days to become familiar with the work content
작업 내용에 익숙해지는 데 며칠 밖에 걸리지 않습니다.
I've been doing digital PR in the past so I'm familiar with
예전에 디지털 PR을 해본 적이 있어서 익숙하다.
-That plan... -I said I'm in charge!
- 그 계획은... - 내가 책임진다고 했어!
This is an important project and I must be responsible for it
이건 중요한 프로젝트이고 내가 책임져야 해
How many times do you want me to speak?
내가 몇 번이나 말하길 바라나요?
You said it only takes a few days to familiarize yourself with the work content?
업무 내용에 익숙해지는 데 며칠밖에 안 걸린다고 했죠?
You said you've been doing it for a long time?
오랫동안 해왔다고 했죠?
Where is it done?
어디서 이루어졌나요?
Are they working for agencies whose names I've never even heard of ?
이름도 들어본 적도 없는 기관에서 일하고 있는 걸까요?
Just because people like you are neither powerful nor trustworthy
너 같은 사람은 힘도 없고 믿음직하지도 않기 때문에
We will distribute your plan to the world, right?
우리는 당신의 계획을 세계에 배포할 것입니다 . 그렇죠?
You should be ashamed
부끄러워해야지
How dare you do it casually...
어찌 감히 아무렇지도 않게 그러시나이까...
I have eight years of relevant work experience, team leader
8년의 관련 업무 경험을 가지고 있으며, 팀장입니다.
No one knows what you did in other companies during those eight years.
당신이 그 8년 동안 다른 회사에서 무엇을 했는지는 아무도 모릅니다.
Even if you have eight years of experience, you may not be as good as Se Rong, a newcomer.
8년 경력을 갖고 있다고 해도 신인 세롱만큼은 아닐 수도 있다.
As far as I'm concerned, there's no difference between you and that newcomer Ji Hyo.
제가 보기엔 당신과 그 신인 지효 사이에는 아무런 차이가 없습니다 .
Do you understand your position now?
이제 당신의 입장을 이해하셨나요?
I still don't agree that you are capable enough to join Serong's public relations team.
나는 아직도 당신이 세롱의 홍보팀에 합류할 만큼 능력이 있다는 데 동의하지 않습니다 .
Agent Park
박요원
Don’t cry in front of me again
다시는 내 앞에서 울지 마
Never negotiate with tears
절대로 눈물로 협상하지 마라
That's the worst way
그게 최악의 방법이야
(The characters, events, groups, organizational backgrounds, etc. in this drama are purely fictitious. We hereby inform you)
(본 드라마 속 등장인물, 사건, 단체, 조직 배경 등은 모두 허구입니다. 이를 알려드립니다.)
Subtitle translation: Wu Jingyi
자막 번역: 우징이